Jesse Packwood

Software Engineer

jesse@lokithewolfdog.com

Summary

Motivated full-stack engineer who values efficiency, diversity, and the ability to contribute to a team. E-commerce experience and a challenging Turing education combine to make a better leader and developer with regards to product innovation and user focus.

Projects

Coin Watch

https://jessepackwood.github.io/ CoinWatch

React, Redux, Firebase

Cryptocurrency tracking web app pulls coincap.io api to watch specific coin performance and track a user generated portfolio.

Movie Tracker

https://github.com/katiescruggs/movie-tracker-frontend

React, Redux, Postgres

Web app utilizing the movieDB api to pull the most recently released films so a user can sign in and favorite films to their account.

SWapiBox

https://github.com/jessepackwood/ swapiBox

React

Star Wars api is used to render data about the movies series characters, vehicles, and planets.

Skills

Techical

Javascript HTML5 Git Node.js
React CSS3 UI/UX Jest/Enzyme
Redux SASS/SCSS Sketch Mocha/Chai

Professional

Activator Collaboration Analytical Adaptability

Experience

The Loki Project

2018 - Present

Web Engineer and Customer service

- Designing and building web pages with image galleries and ecommerce products
- Adobe Lightroom Preset designer and customer service

Merge Global Photography

2018 - 2018

Digital Content Manager and Photographer

- Edited and organized digital content for social media and publications
- Traveled to the Amazon jungle to photograph indigenous people

AAR Aircraft Services

2011 - 2013

2017 - 2018

Material Handler

Oversaw parts inventory and delivery

Education

Turing School of Software and Design

- Graduated from 1708 Front-End Cohort

Indianapolis University of Indianapolis 2010 - 2015

- BA Economics
- Kelley School of Business

+ 1 317 361 0166